I have prepared another Revelation for today.
So this is then the 13th lecture of the seminar Time is the End.
According to the new Booklet, and that 98 of the same name,
which will be the 14th in the series about the last times,
and that is the biggest series we have of Booklets, double more and even more
than, for example, the first creation and fall or the Gospel of love.
In this seminar, so from there and in the Booklet, for now there are two subtopics on the table.
One talks about what the Father intends to do
so that, just before the end, He would provide the possibility of salvation
to those who would otherwise be irretrievably lost,
because due to their pride, materialism and lust
they do not want to admit above Themselves a power to which they would submit
so that it would govern their lives.
So, that He will release the forces of nature in the world where such people live
with an intensity that has not been seen until now
and when their whole world will not only be collapsing
but when it will threaten, defeat them, terrify them
and a number of them will communicate with that Power
they will have enough intelligence to realize that this cannot be by chance
they will respond to the call and will call upon the Name of the Lord.
And if they do it from the heart, they will be delivered according to Acts 2:21.
That would be the first subtopic, we had it today the second lecture
of four planned on this my free day, which would be Monday.
And in this fourth sermon we switch to the other side
and on the other side or the second subtopic of this seminar
and that Booklet for now, is the state of people
which leads or brings to the end.
For me personally, as you have already heard several times,
that is the only necessary and sufficient sign to clearly see
that the end is near, that it cannot be avoided
and in which, end, is present the Father's greatest Love
because otherwise those souls, if they are not stopped by Divine intervention
and redirected though a painful path, which they themselves chose through matter,
again upwards, they would forever continue to fall.
Therefore, the spiritual state of people for me is a sufficient indicator,
a clear proof how much and why the end is near.
Well now, in this Revelation, this is newly translated, I have just translated it,
I have previously prepared and selected them.
In this Revelation, which is revelation 4853,
the Father will point out to us even the very essence of the problem.
By that, what it is that governs people to do what causes their downfall.
And the Revelation is called the spread of sin.
We have in 2 Peter 1:4, I will with this Revelation, this is not a big Revelation,
I will with this Revelation communicate to you also verses from the Scripture, as is proper,
this is not a big Revelation, otherwise there is not... two paragraphs in the receptions of Bertha Dudde,
it is always one Revelation, one sequence, but I have separated this for myself and you,
so it is easier for you to follow the thought.
In 2 Peter 1:4 we have a very important statement, and it says like this:
"having escaped from the corruption that is in the world because of lust."
Because of what is corruption in the world?
By that.
Because of what is this world corrupted?
And if something is corrupted, then it is unusable and does not fulfill its purpose
and then it must be replaced.
I was recently forced to replace an old mixer, a stick one,
for a new one which is much better.
If for nothing else, then because it automatically turns off
when it overheats, which some people do not have enough feeling and
perception, to notice when they mix until it burns out.
Furthermore, that new mixer has something called silent mode,
and that means you can mix even while everyone is sleeping, they won't hear you.
And isn't that progress?
But in any case, that would be the old Earth and the new Earth,
old mixer, new mixer.
When my old mixer burned out, it no longer fulfilled its purpose,
it became unusable and had to be replaced
so that the purpose of me mixing would be fulfilled,
if not for myself,
then a smoothie for her every day, because that's usually how our day starts.
When she wakes up, we go make a smoothie, and a very quality one,
and then we go read the Bible for brave girls or currently I am.
Do we have picture and sound?
So, if you are wondering why the world as a device
which Lord God and our Father uses for mixing fallen beings
to make from them a smoothie, which would be edible for Him and drinkable,
why it broke down, you have the answer in 2 Peter 1:4.
where it says because of lust.
So, corruption is in the world because of lust.
What does that mean?
That means that bodily desires dominate people
thus their spiritual or inner man.
In a way that he is a slave to those bodily desires
and that he is subject to the body fulfilling each of them,
not denying it anything, not withholding from it,
but pleasing it and allowing it,
and thus also himself on that level, to enjoy in that.
That is the reason why the world will perish,
and that means almost everyone. Are you with me?
And to be honest, most of you present here
contribute to that, because your lives are like that too,
and your bellies testify to that.
You can freely say amen.
And since I'm already here, I hope you won't mind,
it also comes to my mind, since we're already in the introductory word,
a famous package of verses, that you more or less know,
because I often quote it,
Colossians 3:5, but also six.
Listen, when it says put to death therefore your earthly members,
that is the opposite of what I said,
that causes corruption in this world,
so the world, the broken mixer, will have to be replaced
for a new, better mixer, called new Heaven, new Earth,
because it is unusable, and a mixer is needed,
unusable, does not fulfill the purpose,
and then it needs to be replaced, because this one is unrepairable.
This Earth and people are unrepairable.
And then it says, this is the opposite,
and therefore if you do not do this, you contribute
to the fact that the end is coming, and that end will be disastrous for you,
if you are like that.
Put to death, therefore, your earthly members,
fornication, impurity, passions,
evil lust and greed, that is also idolatry.
So, the first four are bodily lusts,
greed is a soul disease,
but it also manifests on the bodily level,
because someone can be greedy for food.
And according to that you see what kind of man is in the body,
that he has sin in the body, Romans 7,
and if he does not apply Christ's grace and strength
to mortify his bodily or earthly members,
sin from there, through fornication, impurity,
passion, evil desire and greed, will overcome him
and he will live an unspiritual, natural, material life
in which he will satisfy the body fulfilling its desires appetites and lusts
and in this way spiritually dead under the power of Satan he goes into the abyss.
And since such are the majority, that's why the world is perishing.
Now look, we mention this often, but that's not why I came.
I came because of the sixth verse, and the sixth verse says,
just to find it, I opened several Bibles,
in the sixth verse it says,
because of this comes the wrath of God upon the sons of disobedience.
The wrath of God here is nothing else but the judgment of God, the punishment of God.
So, if you wonder why the wrath of God
and the judgment of God will befall people, that's because of the aforementioned.
Do we have picture and sound? To be honest, I was on the scale,
but it tipped because I followed the guidance, I'm talking about marital fellowship,
and the next seminar, after we finished "Booklet number 57,
the first three Revelations", I chose, if you listened, you heard the continuation,
because we will work on Divine Love, that is taught in church,
and then, but it hangs there, stands in the air,
the continuation also, Booklet number 57,
will be called, that's also "Booklet number 57,
bodily lust must be sacrificed".
That's what it will be called. Bodily lust must be sacrificed.
You know, if you want to live a Divine spiritual way of life,
this bodily lust... I see the need for people to understand this,
because I see for them it's just the body,
or just lust, they don't have an overview of the situation.
That's why it will be called "Booklet number 57,
- bodily lust", in capital letters,
MUST, and again the continuation small," be sacrificed".
Otherwise that sentence is approximately in the Revelation we first covered at this seminar,
3310, Love... Divine... perverted between two people.
And then it says, bodily love must be sacrificed, to the spiritual.
But the sentence I received, which I heard in my spirit,
not audibly, but as a distinct thought that jumped out,
is bodily lust must be sacrificed.
OK, that's also in the topic.
Now let's go to the Revelation from which I believe you will not sleep peacefully,
but that's all right, because if you can't sleep,
that means you have an unclean conscience and you will need to repent.
That's all right, night is an excellent period of time for that,
because usually the noise of the city and the music of your,
I don't know, from YouTube from your phone, music on your channel,
or usually people around you are sleeping,
usually you are like sleeping, so people are silent and you can hear yourself,
so I don't have much compassion and mercy for that
if you don't sleep, I only pray that you use it.
Did someone here write down that we commented on
2 Peter 1:4. Colossians 3 verses 5 and 6.
Write it down so you don't look at me later as if I fell from Mars.
So, Revelation 4853 The Spread of Sin.
The Father says this way, you know that the first sentence is of great importance,
because it determines the direction of the whole Revelation and of course shows us the goal
which we should achieve, about which in the last sentence.
That is the rule of the first and last sentence and praised be Jesus
that it was revealed to Swedenborg.
Sin will prevail and people will live in lust
and sin without a sense of responsibility,
because Satan rules the world and people are in slavery to him.
So, this is obvious.
Obvious.
Especially it is obvious, but I ask you to try to understand.
When it is spoken about lust of the body,
usually it is meant sexual lust, it is part of the package,
but the problem is much deeper.
You know, it is about satisfying that which
the body is made of, and that is the Satanic spirit under judgment,
who in that way rules or continues to rule over the spiritual man.
Whereby this one is in slavery to Pharaoh the king of Egypt
and is spiritually dead.
That state of spiritual death is a missed earthly life
and leads to spiritual ruin.
You know, that is much worse.
You must understand what is happening
at the moment of fulfilling every bodily desire,
even sexual desire.
You know.
I don't know why you are looking at me.
In Proverbs 7:18. but we can also Ecclesiastes 2:1.
Here it speaks about the adulterous woman whose husband went on a journey.
We spoke about that also with Samson.
And a young man of little sense fell under her charms.
She says, come let us get drunk with pleasure until morning
and let us rejoice in the delights of love.
So, to get drunk with pleasure.
A man is in that state intoxicated as far as the spiritual man is concerned,
because bodily pleasure or delight controls his sound mind.
You know.
That must be sacrificed.
And you must understand that in essence,
in order to see where it all shows its ugly snake head.
That will be a seminar on Marriage once I finish
after 100 lectures of this according to Booklet 21.
But Jesus will somehow give me time.
You see that He is cloning me, that I am getting better and better.
And then we have in Ecclesiastes 2:1.
"Then I said in my heart,
let me try pleasure and see what delight provides.
But behold, this also is vanity.
Of laughter I said it is madness, of pleasure what is the use."
And see the second verse.
So, this is quite important to understand what is happening here.
There is pleasure that intoxicates so that you do not think with your spiritual head.
And in that state Satan is your master.
He rules, that state is his child.
And so, blinded because of your wrong love, he leads you to ruin.
And you do not see the light of the Gospel of the glory of Christ who is the image of God.
Because if you saw, then for you this would apply in Psalm 119:47 and 77.
And he says: "In Your commandments is my delight because I love them."
And below it says: "For Your law is my delight."
These are two opposite delights.
And again the first sentence in Revelation 4853.
It says sin will prevail, that is the state in the world,
and people will live in lust and sin without a sense of responsibility.
You see for example that young people are completely lost in space and time.
And I will tell you exactly why that is.
And you unfortunately, since you are of little spiritual sense,
you cannot conclude that yourselves.
Otherwise you would be holding sermons and your voice would be heard far away,
because you couldn't watch that, because you would see that behind that is ruin.
This is how the situation goes for you.
The notorious puberty, when children break free from control
and what parents fear like a nightmare,
is nothing else but sexuality begins to awaken
in the body of a man, a young person and a woman,
which drives them to fulfill their purpose on that level,
because mostly then they are not at all spiritual,
and that is the natural and soul level.
That is an extremely strong drive.
You know? And there they resist authority and framework,
because it limits them in that.
Are you with me?
And now in that state, because often parents unsuccessfully,
fulfill their role of Christ in the family,
so they prepare the children for life, with word and deed and example.
And then in today's time, where all sorts of things are imposed on them,
and parents are to blame because they let them watch all kinds of craziness,
which then become authority for them and those influence them,
then we have this about which we read in Romans,
we will read only the part about perverted sexuality,
but of course it says at the end that it deserves death.
And it says that they, claiming to be wise Romans 1:22, became fools,
they exchanged the glory of the incorruptible God for the image in the likeness of corruptible man
and birds and four-footed animals and reptiles,
and therefore God gave them up in the lusts of their hearts to impurity,
so they dishonor their own bodies,
which should be the temple of the Holy Spirit and that is punishable.
Those who exchanged the truth of God for a lie, worshiped and served the creature
instead of the Creator, we read further down from verse 22 of the first chapter of Romans,
calls them foolish people, they think they are the smartest,
and worshiped and served the creature instead of the Creator
who is blessed forever amen.
And therefore God gave them up, here it is, to shameful passions.
And their women exchanged natural intercourse for unnatural,
and so also men abandoned natural intercourse with a woman
and burned with lust for one another,
so men with men do shameful things
and themselves receive in themselves the due penalty of their error.
Notice that it is about inflamed lust.
That lust is inflamed at an early age,
especially today among young people, and nothing else drives them.
Now, if they are not properly taught, there is the root of the problem.
Because sexuality is very important, but also very strong.
And then, that is the driver.
And with perversion, which is in the world, they very easily perish,
and perversion is obvious in the world because the world is corrupted because of lust.
Above all sexual lust. That guides people above all.
Revelation 1021, second paragraph, that is the natural law,
that is the love which drives us to unite, but on the lowest level.
It drives animalistically, because people on that level are worse than animals.
And then, because of that lust, that is the train of thought, you can clearly follow that,
and as they were not worthy to hold to the knowledge of God,
God gave them over to a debased mind so that they do what is not fitting.
But these are people who are just described, who have sexually strayed.
And then, because of that, they are full of all unrighteousness, malice, greed, evil,
full of envy, murder, strife, deceit, malice.
Because of that is the corruption, which he now describes, because of lust, which he described before.
Malice, whisperers, deceit, slanderers, haters of God, insolent,
drunkards, usurpers, inventors of evil, disobedient to parents,
unreasonable, unfaithful, heartless, merciless, they know God's decree
that those who do such things deserve death, and they not only do them,
but also approve of those who do them. I know such people, they approve of it for their children,
but their punishment will not be late.
You know, you have in 1 Corinthians 6:9 and 10,
and in Galatians 5:19-21, you have the works of the flesh,
and again a good part of that, is carnal lust,
such will not enter the Kingdom of Heaven.
Therefore carnal lust and pleasure must be sacrificed.
Are you with me. But as the world is not able because it is too far gone,
that is the reason for its downfall.
So here, once again the first sentence, then we go to Revelation,
because I could now explain the Bible to you with this view,
from Genesis to Revelation, but then that would divert the sermon in another direction.
Sin will prevail and people will live in lust and sin.
This is a prophetic word that covers the situation, which we clearly see.
This was March 7th, 50. Without a sense of responsibility.
They don't think they will be accountable, but it says below that they will.
They don't think, I look them in the eyes, they don't think they will be accountable.
You know, they are so blinded,
so intoxicated, so succumbed to the adversary, that they don't think they will be accountable.
And then it says, without a sense of responsibility, because Satan rules the world.
Jesus Christ does not rule, Satan.
Jesus rules only where his own have allowed him to rule through them.
But the world is under the power of Satan.
2 Corinthians 4:3 and 4, Luke 4:5-8.
And people are in his bondage.
Period.
That is the reason for Revelation.
And then it says, and they gladly follow his whispers, or his urgings,
weakly and without resistance they succumb to his temptations,
as they fulfill carnal desires.
"Booklet number 57-carnal desire must be sacrificed"
is the seminar that follows when one fine day we close the seminar I announced,
"Serious warnings regarding Christian love for one's neighbor".
Where I will go into the depth of this problem, because I see only shallowness around me.
And watch out.
And it says, they succumb to his temptations fulfilling carnal desires
and have no disgust towards anything.
Or revulsion, repulsion.
While anyone normal should feel disgust towards that.
You know.
Good.
Sin lures them and so people sink into their own mud.
Ok. And now, because of that, period, next thought.
The end is near.
Why? Well, that mixer has burned out.
It does not fulfill its purpose, it is unusable and a new mixer is needed.
That new mixer is called Heaven new Earth.
The end is near.
Anyone who pays attention to the behavior of people,
that would be me, because I really like to observe people,
not to hold it against them, but to see their quality,
to see in relation to the Divine goal and arrangement,
in what relative state and possession they are, because that is my occupation.
Anyone who pays attention to the behavior of people,
also knows what hour has struck.
That the Earth is ripe for destruction.
So, I don't have to look at anything else,
to listen only to the state among people, because of the state in people.
I know when I see that, and I see what time has struck.
And that the Earth is ripe for destruction.
And that people, very important, because everything I say about the state of people
refers to what I will now say,
because I think like that, because that is correct thinking,
and that is in relation to purpose.
If your life does not fulfill the purpose,
your on Earth, your life on Earth has no purpose.
Let's start from the beginning.
If your life on Earth does not fulfill the purpose,
your life on Earth has no purpose.
And then it says,
and that people forget their purpose of life on Earth
and so they stand before the abyss.
So, they balance on the edge of the abyss.
And that is almost all people in the world.
Do not let charismatic gatherings deceive you.
And there too, almost all are like that.
You know, that the Spirit hits them,
that changes them very little.
They are not ready for change, you know.
I don't know why you look at me as if you have never been to a charismatic gathering,
well, you are one of those too.
Did the Spirit, when it laid you on the floor, did it change you?
Of course it did not.
And look, this is a very important sentence,
so we will go back to repeat.
The end is approaching.
Everyone who pays attention,
and should first to themselves, then to people around them,
to the behavior of people,
also knows, does not think,
knows what time has struck.
And that the Earth is ripe for destruction
and that people forget their purpose of life on Earth,
and so, I would say, and therefore they stand before the abyss.
Now, in that state, that is not written, that is written between the lines,
Satan has them completely under his control
and they no longer offer him any resistance.
They acknowledge him as their master
and do what he asks of them.
Now, those people do not think so.
So, when we fulfill the desires, lusts and appetites of our body,
those are all people who eat three meals a day.
You know, those people thereby destroy their spiritual life.
I mean, gluttony and lust are two mortal sins,
so that is nothing new, only people do not know how to connect that with themselves.
You know, maybe they know how to sing songs about the seven deadly sins,
if that exists, maybe there is some rap,
but they cannot connect that with themselves.
We love you, Jesus!
And then they think that none of it concerns them.
If you are that one, that is what Satan wants from you
and by that way he destroys your spiritual life.
And as the majority are like that,
the Earth and the life of people on Earth does not fulfill the purpose
and therefore the end comes,
because that then means destruction of the old, creation of the new,
and then from the beginning.
In sin people will suffocate,
in sin they will perish,
because in the midst of enjoying life
they will find their end as it is written.
It is written when it says it will be like the days of Noah,
because they ate, drank, married, were given in marriage, bought, sold.
And all that until the day when Noah entered the ark,
here Matthew 24, verses 37-39,
we love you Jesus, we can open that here,
just before we also read,
until Noah entered the ark,
and then the flood came and took them all.
And took them all.
And they suspected nothing.
They lived normally.
And we have of course also Revelations on the topic,
just like in the days of Noah,
where it then speaks about how people will enjoy,
give themselves to lusts and pleasures,
and will not care for their spiritual life,
for the purpose of their life.
Alright, just so you know,
if you are among such,
who governs you, what drives you
and where you will end up.
And then it says, well now,
regarding that situation,
it does not seem hard to see this, to understand,
that is why He reveals Himself.
And that is my holy and honorable role
as the one who proclaims this truth.
And I do that regularly,
that is one stream within the Body of the Mission,
it is dedicated to the last days,
that is why the page, now a new look for that page is coming,
so www.ljubavsohladla.com,
that is why almost 600 translated Revelations,
many seminars,
13th, now soon 14th. Library,
now also little videos and picture books,
that is very, very important for you
and the whole world.
And that is why I invite people,
and now someone has to do that out loud,
and that is why I invite people,
that one day all of you will have to answer
for your thoughts, deeds and words.
All of you will be judged
according to your will and your deeds.
Because Jesus says, let's say,
if you will like that in Revelation 22:12.
that behold, I am coming soon,
and with me is the reward to give to all
according to his deeds.
When the books of life will be opened,
Revelation 21, verses 11 and 12,
now we will open that too,
20, verses 11 and 12, pardon, 20,
and I saw a great white throne
and the One who sat on it,
before His face fled,
the earth and the heaven,
and no place was found for them anymore,
and I saw the dead, great and small,
standing before the throne,
and a book, books were opened,
another book was opened,
the book of life,
and the dead were judged
by what is written in the books,
by their deeds.
Verse 13, the sea gave up its dead,
and death and the underworld theirs,
and each was judged by their deeds.
Second Corinthians 5:10 says
that we will all stand before the judgment seat of Christ,
and answer for what we have done in the body,
whether good or evil,
and we should live with that in mind,
and judge our deeds, thoughts,
in relation to the Word of God,
which reveals His will,
and what He considers sin,
and we should consider sin,
and then therefore repent,
and reject, and do it no more,
otherwise we will suffer loss.
Do not fall into sin, it says,
keep yourselves pure,
and despise evil.
That sin does not become
your downfall.
That it does not drag you
into the abyss. So, what will drag people
into the abyss, is sin.
Now then, people
think they are not
sinners, because they have not
killed anyone, and because
they go to church.
It is commendable, if they have not
killed anyone, and even
more commendable, if they go to a living
church, but there are not many of those.
But if
they have not killed anyone,
and go to church,
but are led by
the flesh, they are constantly
in sin, and their
destiny is spiritual death.
And I will show you that now,
and that in three packages of verses.
I will show you
first where it is clearly written,
James 1,
and those verses
14,
we can
13-15, let no one in
to tempt, let no one say God is tempting me,
for God cannot be tempted
by evil, and he tempts no one,
but each one is tempted,
or tested by his own desire,
which draws him and entices him notice,
desire then having conceived
gives birth to sin,
and sin when it is full-grown gives birth
to death. So,
even though they maybe have not
killed anyone, spiritually surely
they have,
and they go to church, and are still spiritually dead,
and go to ruin. If
they indulge the desires
of their flesh, because
no one who lives according to the flesh, will
see life,
that is clearly written in Romans 8:13
where we read, for
if you live according to the flesh, you must die,
but if by the Spirit you put to death
the deeds of the body, you will live.
And we also have Galatians
6:8, and we will open that.
Indeed whoever sows to his flesh
from the flesh will reap
corruption, that means he will perish,
but whoever sows to the Spirit,
from the Spirit will reap eternal life,
and that is again life and death.
And so I will hold
a seminar, so you see what this is really
about in the day,
when you are led
by the flesh, when by the Spirit, Galatians
5:16 and 17,
when you are in grace, when under the law,
the whole context of Romans 8,
and where will not lead you
the works of the flesh, that is into the Kingdom,
and how by the fruits
not of the Spirit in you it is seen that you live
by the flesh. Is that a good plan?
Because it says those who are Christ's,
Galatians 5:24, have crucified
their flesh with its passions and desires,
when the flesh is crucified,
it no longer lives, and then you have
overcome and live by the Spirit.
As almost no one lives by the Spirit,
it is clear that he lives by the flesh, whoever lives
by the flesh, is spiritually dead and cannot
enter the Kingdom, and so the world
perishes, because such a life
by the flesh, absolutely
does not fulfill its purpose,
and thus
becomes purposeless on Earth.
Do not fall into sin,
keep yourselves pure and
despise evil, so that sin does not
become your ruin, so that it does not
drag you into the abyss.
Do not dull
the admonisher within you,
listen to the voice
of conscience, which
warns you about every
bad thought and every
bad deed. You now know
after two seminars,
the bigger and the smaller,
that there is Booklet number 67
voice of the heart, where we have one chapter
about the voice of conscience,
and if you haven't already, it would be good
to have that Booklet on your night
table, because that is your fundamental Booklet
just like the seminar.
Pay attention to its
voice of admonisher
or voice of conscience and follow it.
Do not easily
ignore sin, like well
everyone sins or it's not that terrible?
That would be easy to ignore
sin. Well, here, it is terrible,
the end of the world is coming, that seems to me quite terrible,
because that means the ruin
of many people. Let's do it like this,
the world will perish,
because bodily lust
was not sacrificed
for the sake of spiritual
aspiration.
And then it says,
pay
attention to its voice
of admonisher and follow it.
Do not easily ignore
sin, but remember the One
who will one day judge you.
And we do not like
that word, but still that is
a valid word. Those are
the foundations of Christianity.
And that is the eternal judgment.
One of six
characteristics
of the fundamental doctrine
is judgment.
Judgment.
Those are
Hebrews 6:1 and 2.
We love you Jesus.
And therefore, I think,
it would be good to sometimes mention
judgment.
And that says
eternal judgment.
In Hebrews 6:2.
Eternal judgment.
Therefore judgment is a valid
word. We must live
with an eye on judgment, because we will
be judged by righteousness.
No matter how much
grace is offered to us, we will
be judged by righteousness.
Acts 17:31.
A day is appointed when He will
judge by Christ Jesus by righteousness
people. And then it says
and
pay attention to His voice
and follow Him. Do not easily
ignore sin, but
remember the One who will one day
judge you, who is righteous
and punishes every
sin, because sin
requires compensation
or rather atonement.
If you
live outside of grace, because
you live by the flesh,
there is no atonement
for sin through Christ Jesus.
Therefore everything
you must atone for yourself, suffer
and that is the punishment for sin.
Are you with me?
Ok.
That awaits
all apostates
from Christ.
That is also in
Hebrews, so we can
read in the sixth chapter,
because that is the same
thought.
Because it says
who were once enlightened tasted the heavenly gift
became partakers of the Holy Spirit,
tasted the good Word of God, this is the good Word of God
and the powers of the coming world, which is the power
of the Spirit and the gifts, and then fell away.
It is impossible again
to renew to repentance. When they themselves
again crucify the Son of God,
because they expose Him to ridicule, there is nothing
then of the sacrifice on the cross. And then likewise
we love
you Jesus,
in Hebrews chapter 10,
when it says,
for if willfully 26th
verse, we sin after we have received
knowledge of the truth, there is no more
sacrifice for sins but a fearful
expectation of judgment and wrath,
of fire that will devour
the adversaries. I held a KVP
lecture on the topic that the New Testament
of course has better promises and
it is a better covenant, but it also has a more fearful
punishment. So I
commented on these verses,
because it says, imagine how much
worse punishment than the people
of the Old Testament, and they were executed
on the basis of two or three witnesses,
will deserve the one who tramples the Son of God
and considers unclean the blood of the covenant
by which he was sanctified and the spirit of grace
insults. Who are those? Well, those who go to church,
hear the truth about what is sin and then sin.
Do you know that they don't think
that they are bad people.
They are
servants
of Satan and spiritually dead people
and for them is fire.
That the scripture
says. And now it is necessary to reach them
to save them.
They don't think they need
salvation because they haven't killed anyone and go to church.
You see how
the situation is complicated.
And then it says,
pay attention to his voice
and follow it, the voice
of conscience, the voice of the admonisher,
which is the voice of Christ.
Do not easily ignore sin, but remember the One
who will one day judge you,
who is just and punishes every sin,
because sin requires compensation or
atonement.
Do not allow yourselves to be tempted
by the attractions of the world
and do not fulfill every desire of your
body because it tempts you to sin.
This you must understand.
So, we will take this
as the main
guiding thought of the mentioned seminar,
"Booklet number 57, the lust of the body
must be sacrificed".
That is absolutely not clear to people.
So, he feels
hunger, because he is
used to it, eats, is not hungry at all, because he doesn't know
what hunger is, what it is for,
what feeding is, what is fed,
what is fed with, has no idea what drives him
who controls him and with what
something, he just stuffs himself.
These are spiritually dead people.
The living do not do that.
You know.
Ok.
Do not allow yourself to be
tempted by the attractions of the world
and do not fulfill every desire of your
body, because it tempts you to sin.
Stay pure
and remember that
you cannot stand before My
eyes if you fall
into sin and do not despise it.
So, not only do you move away, you despise.
You despise.
Do you understand?
That means
when you see someone
committing sin, you despise the sin.
You know.
Not the person. He is miserable.
He needs help. The sin. You despise.
That's like, you know, I don't want to
see you, I have nothing to do with you.
I want to destroy you.
I am working on making you disappear.
That is, I despise.
And if that is not your attitude, that is because
you still love sin.
And watch,
stay pure
and remember
that you cannot stand before My eyes
if you fall into sin
and do not despise it.
So, this is very,
very important instruction.
Free yourself
from Satan
who tempts you
if you do not resist him.
How? Well, now I will explain.
Sin has great
power over you
and that is why you should
beware of it because by that
you surrender to my opponent
and you distance yourself
from Me, and that for you
means eternal ruin.
So, the purpose of this
Revelation is
to warn us about the danger
of sin. To show
us under whose power we fall
if
we succumb to sin, to lust,
we indulge the body and where will
bring us to that.
And calls us to
resist. And you would
do well if you took this seriously
because because of this the world is corrupted
and that's why it will perish.
Because of lust.
In the Name of Jesus.
It means perverted
lust, wrong
lust.
In the Name of Jesus.
Those are
almost all the lusts that people know.
In the Name of Jesus.